let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Courteney, Jennifer, David, Lisa, Matthew and Matt make up what?",
    answer: "The cast of Friends",
    options: [
      "The cast of Friends",
      "The cast of Lost",
      "Seinfield",
      "The King of Queens",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "El or Eleven is the central character of which scary Netfilx's series?",
    answer: "Stranger Things",
    options: ["DareDevil", "Narcos", "Stranger Things", "House of Cards"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "La Louver and Musee D'Orsay are famous museuems in which city?",
    answer: "Paris",
    options: ["London", "Paris", "Rome", "Berlin"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Neighbors, the Austrailian TV soap is set on which street?",
    answer: "Ramsey Street",
    options: ["King Street", "Church Street", "High Street", "Ramsey Street"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The Phantom of the Opera is a musical by which composer?",
    answer: "Andrew Lloyd-Webber",
    options: [
      "George Gershwin",
      "Jonathan Larson",
      "Cole Porter",
      "Andrew Lloyd-Webber",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "Fraiser, the multi-award-winning TV show was set in which US city?",
    answer: "Seattle",
    options: ["Seattle", "Denver", "NewYork", "Dallas"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "With Woody the main character, what was the first film created by pixar?",
    answer: "Toy Story",
    options: ["A Bugs Life", "Toy Story", "Finding Nemo", "Monsters Inc."],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The Rijksmuseum can be found in what European City?",
    answer: "Amsterdam",
    options: ["Moscow", "Stockholm", "London", "Amsterdam"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "Acquired by Disney from the famous George for $4 billion in 2012, was which film production house?",
    answer: "Lucasfilm",
    options: ["Lucasfilm", "Star Wars", "Miramax", "DreamWorks"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "Running in the West End since 1952, what is the longest running theater production?",
    answer: "The Mouse Trap",
    options: [
      "Barbershop",
      "The Mouse Trap",
      "The Nutcracker",
      "The Outsiders",
    ],
  },
];
